<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<root>
    <event>        
        <date>02 May 2013</date>
        <title>Dine in the Dark</title>  
        <branch>SBG</branch>    
        <body>Offering a taste of what life is like without sight, Food For Thought hosted a Dine in the Dark at the Gardens with the help of Singapore Association of the Visually Handicapped (SAVH) and community volunteers. While our guests dined in the dark, they also conversed with a mystery guest at their table. Only when the meal was over did they realise that the mystery guests at their tables were visually-impaired.  
            "There is a difference between being blind, and having no vision."  - Mr Leow Chee Tsai, mystery guest</body>
        <image>01</image>
        <image>02</image>   
    </event>    
    <event>    
        <date>April 2013</date>
        <title>Is it Foolish to ... ?</title> 
        <branch>SBG</branch>       
        <body>For the month of April, we held a festival of sharing sessions celebrating the wild ones who chose to walk against the wind and wandered into a whole new way of life. Conversations were shared about chasing their dreams, being a repeat student, whether it was unwise to take a gap year and if it was foolish to pick learning the arts in Singapore. Mystery speakers were invited to share their stories of their own journey down the path less trodden.</body>       
        <image>01</image>
        <image>02</image>
        <image>03</image>
        <image>04</image>
    </event>        
    <event>    
        <date>18 November 2012</date>
        <title>Jacob Ballas Children's Carnival</title> 
        <branch>SBG</branch>
        <body>Food For Thought took part in the Jacob Ballas Children's Carnival 2012 to help raise funds to expand the Children's Garden in Singapore Botanic Gardens. Celebrating the spirit and fun of being a child, we served little hot-dog buns, mini burgers and a childhood camping favourite – grilled bananas drizzled with chocolate! All profits raised from the Carnival were given towards the expansion of Children's Garden.</body>
        <image>01</image>
        <image>02</image>
        <image>03</image>
    </event>    
    <event>    
        <date>25 August 2012</date>
        <title>Ben &amp; Jerry's Chunkfest</title>         
        <branch></branch>
        <body>Food For Thought was invited to be one of Ben &amp; Jerry's Fairness Partners at their annual Chunkfest Fairness Village, held at Sentosa Siloso Beach for 2012. In line with celebrating the spread of 'Peace, Love and Ice-Cream', we chose our 'Give Clean Water' cause as the beneficiary. Since 2010, our 'Give Clean Water' cause has given more than 6500 Africans access to clean water. All of our profits from Ben &amp; Jerry's Chunkfest 2012 were given towards the same cause, continuing to fund the well-building projects by Living Water International.</body>
        <image>01</image>
        <image>02</image>
        <image>03</image>
    </event>
    <event>    
        <date>13 July 2012</date>
        <title>National French Fry Day</title> 
        <branch></branch>
        <body>13 July marks National French Fry Day and Food For Thought has made it a long-standing tradition to give out a cup of free fries to customers. Why? Simply 'cause Fryday we're in love.</body>
        <image>01</image>
        <image>02</image>
        <image>03</image>
        <image>04</image>
    </event> 
    <event>    
        <date>17 June 2012</date>
        <title>Father's Day</title> 
        <branch></branch>
        <body>Food For Thought wanted to give Dads some love this Father's Day! We gave out 'Best Dad in the World' coupons which were redeemable for a range of special gifts, from a heartfelt long talk over a cuppa to a simple hug, and even inclued a free Hoegaarden beer on the house!</body>
        <image>01</image>
        <image>02</image>
    </event>
    <event>    
        <date>4 June 2012</date>
        <title>Love is Loud</title> 
        <branch>SBG</branch>
        <body>Food For Thought helped to host 'Love is Loud', an all-girls party organised by Blessings in a Bag (BiaB), at the Gardens. BiaB, a non-profit organisation with the belief that every person deserves the opportunity to rise above, collaborated with Self-Help International Network Enterprise (SHINE) Singapore to create mentorships for young girls at-risk and paired each of them with an older girl volunteer. Over homely dishes provided by Food For Thought, warm conversations were shared and new friendships forged. Other highlights of the event included a special photo-booth setup, a craft corner to customise your very own thank-you cards and a heartfelt performance by Charles, a Melbourne-based musician. All in all, it was an afternoon well spent with good people and good food for a good cause!</body>
        <image>01</image>
        <image>02</image>
        <image>03</image>
        <image>04</image>
    </event>
    <event>    
        <date>24 April 2012</date>
        <title>Walk For Water</title> 
        <branch>SBG</branch>
        <body>Giving Clean Water has always been a cause close to Food For Thought's heart. When Aveda Singapore organised a Walk for Water to raise awareness about fatal water-borne illnesses from unsafe drinking water as part of Earth Day 2012, we walked together to support this movement. This walk is symbolic of the average distance women in developing countries have to walk each day to collect water for their families. After the walk, participants were invited to enjoy a hearty breakfast buffet at Food For Thought at the Gardens.</body>
        <image>01</image>
        <image>02</image>
        <image>03</image>
    </event>  

   


 





 

 

  
    
</root>
